{
    "id": "db42b7b387cf4aa0a457ed76419251fd",
    "title": "Tenses exercise for intermediate level",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6ad8d08034fa4800a2d265ce04d4b04e",
            "title": "Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… sleep well yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can't",
                        "couldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The train .....................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has just left",
                        "had just left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. college last year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "left",
                        "was leaving",
                        "have left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The light …………………. out while I was reading.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went",
                        "goes",
                        "go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The light always …………………. out when I am about to study.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "goes",
                        "has gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ..................... the piano when I met her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was playing",
                        "played",
                        "has played"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you ever ………………… to Singapore?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "been",
                        "be",
                        "being"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Every morning, he ....................... for a walk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "goes",
                        "go",
                        "has gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team …………………. the West Indies yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "defeated",
                        "was defeated",
                        "had defeated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. several books.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has written",
                        "had written",
                        "wrote"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}